wovn.io 2017-05-19

# WOVN.io | Localize your website.

## Section I. Definitions.

For the duration of this privacy policy, the following terms have the following definitions and meanings:

Cookie – A small piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user's browser (e.g. Mozilla Firefox or Internet Explorer) while the user is browsing that website.

Encrypted hash – A method of storing a password which is considered practically impossible to invert, that is, to recreate the input data from its hash value alone rather than a simple encryption. In other words, it is very secure.

Hosting – The process of uploading your data to our servers so it can be stored and displayed in many different languages.

Information - Information you provide us or information we collect from you that could be used to personally identify you. Examples include IP addresses, name, email address, etc. Additionally, this is what the primary focus of this document is.

Internet Protocal Address (IP) - A numerical label assigned to a device participating in a computer network that uses the Internet Protocol for communication. An IP address serves two principal functions: host or network interface identification and location.

JavaScript – A standard software programming language used on most modern websites.

Metadata - Provides information about a certain item's content. For example, an website may include metadata that describes how large the picture is, the color depth, the image resolution, when the image was created, and other data.

You / Your – Refers to the user and end-user of this website.

Third Party – Individuals, entities, websites, services, products, and applications that are not controlled, managed, or operated by us. This includes other users and independent organizations or groups who help promote, pay for, advertise on, or have any other non-controlling interest in WOVN. This may include translators.

We, Us, and Our: Refers to WOVN.IO and its partners that incorporate this policy. Please note that this term does not necessarily represent independent translators or other external stakeholders.

## Section II. Application of This Policy.

Our privacy policy applies to all of the services offered by us, but might exclude services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this document, such as external translation companies that you may use. This privacy policy is the same, regardless of any language. Please note that in the event of any differences in meaning or interpretation between the original English version of this Privacy Policy and a translation, the original English version takes precedence. Our privacy policy does not cover the information practices of third parties who advertise our services. This policy also does not cover any information linked to our site through any other, for example, by signing in from your Facebook account, any information processed through Facebook directly would be covered by their privacy policy. Any content on your sites, or other publicly uploaded information, can be seen by everyone and is therefore not covered by this policy. By using our services you are agreeing to this policy in its entirety, as well as our Terms of Service. NOTE: Our Terms of Service will be shortly forthcoming.

## Section III. Information You Give Us.

The purpose of WOVN.IO is to expand information on the Internet to a wider variety of people, cultures, and countries that may otherwise be limited by language barriers. In essence, we seek to share your web content with the world. In order to do that, we must gather and store specific pieces of information that you share with us. Examples of this information include, but are not necessarily limited to:

  1. Email and password of your account;
  2. Content of uploaded sites;
  3. Translated content of uploaded sites through third parties;
  4. Financial information used to pay for manual translation (for the specific details on this, including your rights and protections, please see our Terms of Service; and,
  5. Any other information you share with us.

This information is the bare minimum required to use our services. We strive to keep this information at a minimum to ease the use of our services as well as increase the amount of privacy for our users.

## Section IV. Information We Collect Automatically.

Examples of the information we collect automatically include, but are not necessarily limited to:

  1. Internet protocol (IP) address;
  2. Certain computer information your browser or computer automatically provides us with (this might be information such as browser type, version, plug-ins, etc);
  3. The time, date, and signature of your account when you sign-in and sign-out;
  4. The content of your sites that are stored on our servers;
  5. The translated content of your sites that are stored on our servers;
  6. External sign-in data from other sites such as Facebook or Twitter;
  7. Any other information automatically gathered. This is often performed by using information gathered through the use of cookies, javascript, and other methods.

## Section V. Information We Do Not Collect.

We do not collect the following information:

  1. Meta-data of your web content;
  2. Site content sharing; and,
  3. Specific personal information that is not absolutely required for the use of our services.

## Section VI. Protection of Your Information.

We collect very little personal information about you and we do not rent or sell your information to third parties. Additionally, we are not actively viewing your uploaded content for any information. We may use common technologies to collect information about how you use our service. For example, we use cookies to track your use of our service to verify that your account is valid. We also store your language preferences using a cookie. We use this information to enhance your user experience, perform maintenance on our code and translations, and to develop new features. These are used in a positive manner to help our services run smoothly and are not shared. Once we receive information from you, or information about you through automatic means, we keep it until your use of our services has ended.

It is our official policy to not reveal your information to any party (third or otherwise) unless absolutely necessary (see Section VIII for certain exceptions). We strive to protect your information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We use a variety of technical procedures (such as storing your passwords in an encrypted hash) designed to protect our systems and your information. Your information is important to you and your privacy is important to us.

While we make every effort to secure your information, there may be extreme unauthorized exceptions (such as digital piracy or illegal violations of our policy). In such circumstances we will make every effort to protect your information to the best of our ability and comply with the law of your applicable country when necessary.

## Section VII. Your Rights.

We may share your information with your consent. It is your right to discontinue our services at any time. You always have the right to disable cookies and other tracking methods on your own browser. If you do, it may cause errors with the site's use. You also have the right to request any content to be removed from our servers at any time.

## Section VIII. Our Right and Obligations.

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. You will always be able to view this policy and any changes to it whenever you wish. Unfortunately, there are certain conditions where we must share your information. However, these situations are very limited and include the following situations:

  1. Meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request;
  2. Comply with any court orders or mandates from legal authorities;
  3. Enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations;
  4. Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues;
  5. Protect against harm to our rights, property, and safety;
  6. To protect the rights, property, and safety of our users;
  7. Protect our organization, infrastructure, employees, and contractors;
  8. Prevent serious harm or death to a person; and,
  9. Any other extreme or extenuating circumstance that may warrant the sharing of your information.

## Section IX. Closing.

Thank you for reading our Privacy Policy. Please remember, the purpose of this information is to provide your web content to the world. WOVN.IO has no interest in your personal information other than fulfilling the mission of translation and that of your site's own mission. We hope you enjoy using our service and spread your web content across the globe.
